<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kevin M. Counts</title>
    <link>https://countdigi.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kevin M. Counts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://countdigi.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Readline and Fuzzy Finder</title>
      <link>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2021/08/readline-and-fuzzy-finder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2021/08/readline-and-fuzzy-finder/</guid>
      <description>In my bioinformatics work, I often find myself maintaining a text file with commands, options, and paths relevant to the tasks I am working on. I have a workflow to yank a selection from this text file into an intermediate file and then use the fc builtin to copy the selection onto my command prompt. This workflow works well but I wanted to improve it even more increasing efficiency.
After some experimentation I was inspired by the fzf (Fuzzy Finder) project and it&amp;rsquo;s use of readline bindings for looking up your shell history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy cd for project dirs</title>
      <link>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2020/01/fuzzy-cd-for-project-dirs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2020/01/fuzzy-cd-for-project-dirs/</guid>
      <description>When working between projects, I realize that I almost always repeat the same few tasks including:
 Typing cd &amp;lt;path&amp;gt; to enter the project directory Typing git fetch or git pull to check/merge any changes upstream Typing &amp;lt;Ctrl&amp;gt;-b , while in tmux to rename the window to the project name  By incorporating the wonderful command-line fuzzy finder fzf I wrote a small bash function called cdp to automate these steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast AI</title>
      <link>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2019/12/fast-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://countdigi.github.io/post/2019/12/fast-ai/</guid>
      <description>I came across a great episode while listening to Software Engineering Radio the other day while on my morning walk.
Episode 391 features Jeremy Howard from fast.ai explaining deep learning from concept to implementation.
I had heard of fast.ai before in an Elixir meetup where I met a gentlemen who designs machine learning systems for monitoring people in hospital beds. The system uses visual detection aided by deep learning to alert staff if a patient has fallen from their bed hopefully getting the patient the help they need more quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
